{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Igneous%20rocks%20are%20formed%20by%20excessive%20heat%20and%20pressure.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Salt%20is%20100%25%20composed%20of%20Sodium.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An%20atom%20contains%20a%20nucleus.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An%20exothermic%20reaction%20is%20a%20chemical%20reaction%20that%20releases%20energy%20by%20radiating%20electricity.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An%20average%20human%20can%20go%20two%20weeks%20without%20water.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Celiac%20Disease%20is%20a%20disease%20that%20effects%20the%20heart%2C%20causing%20those%20effected%20to%20be%20unable%20to%20eat%20meat.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Psychology%20is%20the%20science%20of%20behavior%20and%20mind.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Water%20always%20boils%20at%20100%C2%B0C%2C%20212%C2%B0F%2C%20373.15K%2C%20no%20matter%20where%20you%20are.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Not%20including%20false%20teeth%3B%20A%20human%20has%20two%20sets%20of%20teeth%20in%20their%20lifetime.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science%20%26%20Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A%20plant%20that%20has%20a%20life%20cycle%20for%20more%20than%20a%20year%20is%20known%20as%20an%20annual.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]}